



#### ABOUT ME

I am a creative and genuine person, a motivated and goal-oriented individual with experience in customer contact and sales. Strong communication skills in B2B as well as B2C and accustomed to working in fast paced environments maintaining an eye for detail.

# CONTACT



### Skills

Stress resistent
Swedish – native
English – Fluent in writing and
verbal

#### **CERTIFICATE**

Prices for immaculate sale results

Currently taking CS50 Harvard course

A2 french

A2 italian



## Work experience

Dec 2021 - current

Product coordinator, claim/customer service representative

Nordic Nest, Kalmar

**Communication:** Excellent verbal and written communication skills, strong rhetoric, and quick thinking. Experienced with long-term customer contacts and returning customers.

**Customer service:** Strong ability to identify and understand customer needs and wishes, amazing client relationship management.

**Sales:** Sales-oriented, proficient in upselling, and ready for negotiations when the possibilities arise.

**Language:** Fluent in Swedish and English; Basic knowledge of Spanish and currently improving it for several reasons.

**System understanding:** Freshworks, CRM, Navision, Bitlog, Office365, JIRA, Merchant center, inriver (PIM), excel

Nordic Webhelp, Kalmar

Retention agent, technical support Sep 2019 - 2021 aug

**Communication:** Helped customers transition from "I want to cancel" to continuing their journey with us, building long-term beneficial business relations. On a daily basis helping the customer see why are worth their hard worked money and energy. Often turning a customer boiling with anger to the most gentle hearted person. This i achieved through rhetoric techniques and the right mindset.

**Customer service:** Assisted customers with fiber/satellite troubleshooting. **Sales:** Strong focus on sales, upselling, and sales analysis during conversations. **Important acquired skill:** Resilience and perseverance, always seeing possibilities where one might there aren't any.

#### Education

Technology and Information Science

Aug 2016 - 2019 June

Fria läroverken, Kalmar

**Acquired skills:** With great interest in programming and with tech I have develop ed a curious mind with efficiency seeking. Making sure to learn from every interaction.